integrity is like doing the right thing
and no one's watching and um so
basically like when no one's watching
you out in the basketball court you can
practice to get better and stuff and you
don't have to like do it when somebody
makes you do it
i think integrity just means having like
good character and good intentions um in
what you're doing this means like
courage like you don't want to get mad
at something you want to try to go
through it doing the right thing even
when no one's watching even if things
are hard or even if you don't get your
way in sports that you shouldn't just
quit or be a
not such a good person i think you
should even if it gets hard you should
just look through it
[Music]
you